if there are so few of us left, Abazi Nav, yes
если нас абази нав осталось так мало да
Why are you going to die for this Russian Empire
Зачем вы идёте за Российскую империю эту
You don't know the Russian
умирать Ты плохо знаешь Российскую
Empire well, honestly look At our ancestors
империю честно смотри В наших предков
Yes Russian troops of our grandparents
Да русские войска наших бабушек дедушек
Yes Azino And you now instead of us there
Да Азино А ты сейчас вместо у нас
are 23,000 left instead of us
осталось 23.000 вместо того чтобы мы
taking care of our family Yes  you go Moscow
берегли свой род Да ты идёшь Москва
look Muscovites are sitting in clubs And you
смотри москвичи сидят по клубам А вас
Azino in short they throw you to die somewhere in
Азино короче кидают умирать где-то в
Ukraine
Украине
about the American
о американский
flag you are quite insightful and what do you
флаг вы довольно проницательный а чём
talk about
общаетесь
yes on any topic you are a
да на любую тему вы
military man I am not I am from the Caucasus Well Russia I
военный Я нет я из Кавказа Ну Россия Я
love Russia from the Caucasus And where from the
Россию люблю из Кавказа А откуда из
Caucasus  cha Circassian Republic KCR
Кавказа ча Черкесская республика КЧР
understood you are swinging or Circassian I am
понял вы качается или черкес я
Abazin small nationality I know Abazin
абазин малая народность я знаю абазы
Abazins my father is
абазины у меня отец
Abazin
абазин
what my father is from Abazinsky
чего у меня отец из из абазинского
region yes Abazin
района да абазин
he yes surname a a
он да фамилия
surname Can I know your surname
а а фамилия Можно твою фамилию узнать
my surname
моя фамилия
NBA lba dzin
НБА лба дзин
ba  lba dzin ba
ба лба дзин
d zl bal lba n n n Nina Nina Boris
ба д зл ба лба н н н Нина Нина Борис
Anton
Антон
NBA lba
НБА лба
dzin Denis Zinaida Irina Dzi then
дзин Денис Зинаида Ирина Дзи потом
Natalia Boris Andrey dzin NBA NBA Well,
Наталия Борис Андрей дзин НБА НБА Да ну
that's actually u na Princely family
это это вообще-то у на Княжеская фамилия
Well, I don't know, I don't know because my
Ну не знаю не знаю потому что у меня
father died  when I was 3 years old yes, that
отец умер когда было мне 3 года да то
is, I didn't really meet him And it
есть я его как бы уже не застал А мать
turns out that my mother was Belarusian and I am
получается она была белоруска и я
half Abazin half Belarusian I
наполовину абазин наполовину Белорус Я
just
просто
am the second Abazin I have met
я вы второй абазин которого я встречал
In all the time on chatroulette
За всё время в чатрулетке
NBA Yes NBA NBA NBA it is written like this
НБА Да НБА НБА НБА оно вот так пишется
NBA
НБА
Well, that's a princely family name, it's really
Да ну это Княжеская фамилия вообще
cool, maybe I'm one of the
прикольно то может я из
princes Well, you know how the Soviet
князей Ну ну знаешь как нас Советский
Union smeared us all, actually
Союз всех размазал вообще-то
Yes, my father As my mother
Да у меня отец Как говорит мать
says, Why does my father,
рассказывает Почему отец
uh, I'm originally from Belarus Yes, but now I
э Я сам из Белоруси родом Да но сейчас
live in the United States of America,
живу в Соединённых Штатах Америки
it turns out  that there a little bit Under the
получается что там немножко При
Soviet Union oppressed us Circassians
Советском Союзе притеснять нас черкесов
and Abaz gov and Azino and you don't  Circassian
о и абаз гов и Азино и ты не черкес
Circassian and Abazin are two different things No
черкес и абазин - это две разные вещи Не
well, look, we are all the same, we are
ну как смотрите мы всё равно мы все
all Adyghe, we are all Adyghe,
Адыги мы все Адыги
Dyghe, how very sad for me that you don’t know
дыги как мне очень сно что ты не знаешь
that Adyghe and
что Адыги и
look, they are two different things No well, [ __ ], I won’t say
смотри две разные Не ну сри не я скажу
how, how I think that we are Abazins
как как я считаю что мы абазины
separate people the closest people to us
отдельный народ самый близкий к нам
are the Apsua
народ - это апсуа
Abkhaz and then there are our relatives
абхазы вот дальше ещё наши родственники
Adyghe Kabarda Well we have all this no no We are
Адыги Кабарда Ну мы всё это нету нету Мы
co-religionists we are all Circassians we are all Circassians
единоверцы мы все черкесы мы все Черкес
we are Azgi Abazy Abazy yes it's like look there
мы азги абазы абазы да это как смотри
are Slavs they are divided into Russians
есть славяне они делятся на русских
Ukrainians Belarusians Poles and so on  what do
украинцев белорусов Поляков та что у
you have there this this
тебя вот там вот это вот
this
это
on your you don't say that
вот на на твоей ты ты так не говори
look
смотри
uh the US supports the Circassians Yeah
э США поддерживают черкесов Да
yeah everyone and admits that the Russian
агов всех и признаёт что Российская
Empire committed genocide of the Circassians and the
империя сделала геноцид черкеса и
peoples of the Caucasus you know And do you know
народов Кавказа понимаешь А ты знаешь
that the Russians themselves support all this
что и русские сами это всё поддерживают
and ours
и наш
language We are my children I
язык Мы у меня дети я сам свой язык
personally don’t know my language but  me
лично не знаю но меня
My Russia my government forces me to
Моя Россия моя власть заставляет мой
learn my language and my children exactly the
язык учить и моих детей точно так
same way I understood
же понял
you honestly Can you can
тебе честно сказать А можешь можешь Вот
I'm interested I just haven't heard Yes how
мне интересно я просто не слышал Да как
our language sounds can you tell me on
наш язык звучит можешь сказать по
Abbass Abaz will be
аббасс абазы будут
free just like
свободные аж прям как
on Abaz Mbit
на Абаза Мбит
Mbit Mbit Cool  Do you know the Abaza
Мбит Мбит Круто Ты знаешь абазинский
language after Chinese the most difficult in the
язык после китайского самый сложный в
world Yes I
мире Да это я
heard you know There is such a thing what is your
слышал знаешь Есть такое вот как тебя
name
зовут
m And can I know your name Well they did
м А можно узнать твоё имя Ну меня
n't name me Basque they called me Lenya
назвали не по Баски меня назвали Лёня
Leonid Leonid Leonid
Леонид Леонид Леонид
NBA
НБА
Lenin I don't
Ленин Я не
know no Don't think about it  beautiful
знаю не Ты не подумай у тебя красивое
good
хорошее
name you know there is such an AYZ
имя знаешь есть такой вот айз
and if you learn it like this how to communicate with other people
и если выучит так как с другими людьми
well swear you will quickly
общаться ну ругаться ты быстро его
learn it you know how
выучишь знаешь как
it is Look I can tell you My name is
оно Смотри вот могу сказать Меня зовут
Azamat you are
Азамат тебя
cool
прикольно
Daro
Даро
honestly I
честно у
have Leonid And my father's name was jum
меня Леонид А у меня отца звали джум
jum jum jum I  leoni ju
джум джум джум я леони Джу
and
а
now i'll tell you my grandfather's name was
деда сейчас скажу деда звали у меня
t damn well this is old
Т Блин ну это старый
you know my father turns out he
знаешь у меня отец получается Он
would be bro if we don't these words
бы Бро если мы не будем эти слова
nobody will raise these words
поднимать никто эти слова не поднимет
if we don't translate it somehow
если не будем это как-то что-то
our nation does
переводить наша нация понима
n't understand And
не А
you know the Azizi there are only 35,000 of us
азизи ты знаешь нас всего 35000 человек
and very few Yes in Kocha Cherkessia
да очень мало Да в коча Черкесии
a little bit and so and a little bit more everything You
немножко и так и ещё чуть-чуть всё Ты
understand that the Abazi -  this is me to you I if
понимаешь что абази - это я тебе я если
you here google azam
ты вот загугли азама
drov where ho zagu
дров где хо загу
these are the most warlike people warlike
это самые воинственные люди воинственные
you Azamat what
теб Азамат какой
Jam
Джем
genres Azamat genres so there is Facebook
жанров Азамат жанров так есть Facebook
genres Azamat Zaurovich Oh these are Ukrainians
жанров Азамат Заурович О это украинцы
Tina Peacemaker Yes Russian war
Тина Миротворец Да российский военный
criminal and murderer
преступник и убийца
writes I am a war criminal and murderer yes
пишет Я военный преступник и убийца да
Yes  writes It's you
Да пишет Это ты
who got it I understand writes e date of birth
зау это я понял пишет э дата рождения 6
February 6 ninetieth year yes yes yes yes it's
февраля девяностого года да дада да это
me Cool
я сам Прикольно
yes getting wounded in twenty-third
да получение ранения в двадцать третьем
year near Kurdyumov where I got wounded
году под курдюмов кой получил ранение
Yes this is the
Да это
second I had it was a diagnosis of MVT
второе у меня это было диагноз мвт
shrapnel wound of the chest limbs are
осколочные ранение груди конечности
blind non-penetrating wound  scapular
слепы непроникающие ранение лопаточной
region on the left yes
области слева да
cool yes no problem at all
прикольно да вообще без проблем я
I I can't understand look if there are
Я не могу понять смотри если нас Азино
so few of us Azino left yes Why are you going to die for
осталось так мало да Зачем вы идёте за
this Russian Empire
Российскую империю эту
You don't know the Russian
умирать Ты плохо знаешь Российскую
Empire well honestly look at our ancestors Yes
империю честно смотри наших предков Да
Russian troops our grandparents Yes
русские войска наших бабушек дедушек Да
Abazi Nav And now you are instead of us
абази нав А ты сейчас вместо у нас
23,000 are left instead of us
осталось 23.000 вместо того чтобы мы
taking care of our family Yes, you and
берегли свой род Да ты и
Muscovites are sitting in clubs And you, Azino,
москвичи сидят по клубам А вас Азино
in short, are being thrown out to die somewhere in Ukraine And
короче кидают умирать где-то в Украине а
you know that the Abazis are the most powerful family in the
ты знаешь что абази самый вый род
Caucasus You are talking
Кавказа самый вый ты пори
about if they were warlike they
с если бы они были са воинственные они
would have rebelled  against Russia and so
бы восстали против России а так
they we are not slaves zapm rana All we are not
они мы не рабы запом рана Все мы не
slaves my children are forced to learn Abaza
раб моих детей заставляют абазинский
Russian Russian are forced
русский русский заставляют моих детей
to learn Abaza language and you put on This
абазинский язык учить а ты одел Вот это
yellow This with a
жёлтое Вот это с
trident
трезубцем
understand Look you yes
понима Смотри ты да
Azamat Azamat kazima tovi from this from
Азамат Азамат казима тови из этой из
Karachay-Cherkessia Yes  you are Abazin  of which
Карачаево Черкесии Да ты абазин которых
there are fewer left than Indians Yes in the USA and
осталось меньше чем индейцев Да в США и
instead of living you build a house for
ты вместо того чтобы жить строи дом
your children do you even have children
своих детей дети вообще у тебя есть
Wait Can I tell you I live I
Подожди Можно тебе сказать я я живу Я
live on a reservation I have a reservation Yes
живу в резервации у меня резервация Да
we live on a reservation look Wait So the
мы живём в резервации смотри Подожди Так
Azamatovich store Do you have children
магазин азаматович У тебя дети
yes yes two How
есть да двое Сколько им
old are they How do I know you can want my
лет Откуда я знаю ты можешь хочешь моих
not just how old are your children I
не просто сколько твоим детям лет Мне
wonder how old they are Why are
интересно насколько они взрослые Почему
you asking me like that because look
ты так меня спра потому что смотри
because Russia Yes wants them
потому что Россия Да хочет чтобы у них
not to have a dad Yes so that you are somewhere in  steppes of
не было папы Да чтобы ты где-то в степях
Ukraine and everything and you were not there yes you are not a
Украины и всё и тебя не было да ты вы не
warlike people maybe once you were a
воинственный народ может когда-то были
warlike people you were destroyed by the
воинственный народ вас уничтожила
Russian Empire divided you and
Российская империя разделила вас да и
made you their own sco in Tui lives how many
сделала вас своими ско в туи жит сколько
Azino in Turkey Why who
Азино в Турции Почему кто их
expelled them explain who expelled Azino to
изгнал объясни кто изгнал Азино в
Turkey  don't wait and where are you from Abazin?
Турцию не подожди а ты абазин откуда
Can you find out from Turkey? No, from the Abazin
Можно узнать с Турции нет из абазинского
region of Karachay Cherkessia My
района карачаева Черкесии Мой
father is not And where are you from? I myself am a
отец не А ты откуда сам выходец я сам
father from Karachay Cherkessia. I came to
отец из карачаева Черкесии приехал в
Belarus in Minsk in  Soviet Union
Беларусь в Минск в Советском Союзе
to study here met my mother I was born in
учиться тут встретил маму Я родился в
Belarus
Беларуси
Bro well I don't know honestly Well how else can I
Бро ну я не знаю честно Ну как тебе ещё
tell you Look I opened Wikipedia yes
сказать Смотри я открыл Википедию да
Abazins in Turkey 50-80 000 Abazins nav
абазины в Турции 50-80 000 абази нав
more than in Russia who expelled them to
больше чем в России кто их изгнал в
Turkey Azino from their native
Турцию Азино со своих родных
places wait  are
мест подожди
you a
ты
Muslim No I am not a
мусульманин Нет я
believer you are not a believer Well
неверующий ты неверующий Ну я в
I grew up in the Soviet Union I
Советском Союзе вырос меня как бы там
was not there yet Islam like in
еще не было у нас Ислама типа в
Belarus I was born in the Soviet Union so
Беларуси я родил в Советском Союзе то
look how it happens yes That the Abazis
смотри как так получается да Что абази
were expelled from their native places in Turkey
изгнали из своих родных мест в Турции
now lives more Azino  than in Russia
сейчас живёт больше Азино чем в России
yes in Russia
да в России
they gave I live where I lived And why do
дали Я живу там где я жил А почему в
a bunch of Abazins live in Turkey
Турции живут э куча абазин
why because there was a Russian-Caucasian
почему потому что была русско-кавказская
war and the Abazins surrendered Yes you have an
война так и абазины сдались Да у тебя
American flag behind you
сзади американский флаг
So where did the Indians go the same as the
Так куда делись индейцы так так же как и
Abazins everything  the Americans conquered them
абазины всё американцы их завоевали так
and so you Abazins, it turns out you surrendered to the
и вы абазины получается вы сдались
Russians and now you kiss their portraits
русским и теперь ихние портреты да
Yermolov's troops simply tortured our Abazin grandmothers and
ермоловские наших абазинских бабушек и
grandfathers in large numbers, nobody
дедушек просто в массовых количествах
harnessed my grandfather, nobody, my
запрягали мого дедушку никто моего
grandmother, grandfather,
бабушку дедушку
look, look at the description of
никто посмотри посмотри описание
historians. Yes, they say that Yermolov's
историков Да говорят что ермоловские
troops harnessed Abazin
войска запрягали абазинских
men in carts, there were a
мужчин в повозках было во
hundred, they tortured them, and now you
сто издевались над ними и ты сейчас ты
just know, let's say, If you had
просто знаешь скажем Если бы ты имел
conscience if you
совесть если ты
were let's say a proud son of the Caucasus Yes you would
был скажем гордым сыном Кавказа Да ты бы
n't fight for those who conquered you from the Caucasus I'm
не воевал за тех кто тебя заво Кавказа я
under an American contribution and under
под американским вкладом и под
this windbreaker with a
это ветровкой с
trident what do you what do you Azi scha
трезубцем что тебе что тебе Ази сча
cherke made ameri iu
черке сдела амери иу
what do you
что ты
sets don't even understand what kind of trius
сеты даже не понимаешь что за триус у
you have  under
тебя под
the chin explain what kind of trident is this
подбородком объясни что это за трезубец
trident Yes,
трезубец Да
this is the meaning of it on the coins of Prince Vladimir
это смы он на монетах князя Владимира
who baptized Rus Great Rus that's
который Русь крестил Великую Русь вот на
what kind of fascism is on the coins This is
монетах какой фашизм Это
Kievan Rus which is the
г Киевскую Русь которая
Great Prince Vladimir to whom
Великий князь Владимир которому
all the lands belonged and the Tmutarakan
принадлежали все земли и тмутараканское
principality which  to whom
княжество который которому абазы
did the Abazins swear allegiance, the Abazins swear allegiance to Prince
присягнули абазины присягнули князю
Vladimir and I know who
Владимиру и яде я знаю кто кому
swore allegiance to whom Yes, the Abazins I live here, live here, come
присягнул Да абазины я здесь живу зде
here to
живёт сюда прие Владимиру Да князю
Vladimir Yes, they swore allegiance to Prince Vladimir and said that they
Владимиру присягнули и сказали из покон
will worship Kiev from time immemorial
веков будут Киеву поклоняться
You hear me, come here and
они Ты слышь меня ты сюда приедь и на
see this
это посмотри
Why are you giving up  I come If you
Ты сда зачем мне приезжать Если вы там
became there I came to America This is a free
стали Я приехал в Америку Это свободная
country I am an Abazin here a person and you are Abazins
страна я абазин тут человек а вы абазины
Well how am I half Abazin I am half Abazin half
Ну как я полу абазин я полу абазин полу
Belarusian And you Abazin get yes you
Белорус А ты абазин получаешь да ты
live in your own on the land of your ancestors
живёшь в своей на земле своих предков
Bro you are on Yurki
Бро ты по Юрки
Turks pot Yes  I study Turkish I
тюрки потр Да я турецки изучаю я турецки
study Turkish Turks our brothers
изучаю турки наши братья
Turks
турки
Turks Turks have sheltered how many of our
турки турки приютили сколько наших
ancestors have you
предков
sheltered and
приютили и
you don't know your language You know
ты свой язык не знаешь Ты знаешь
Turkish you are not Azin
турецкий ты не азин
Remember this you are not Azin You betrayed your
Запомни это ты не азин Ты предал своих
ancestors The
предков
leader of the Circassian people will liberate the
Лидер черкесского народа освободит
Caucasus Erdogan is a Turkic people you
Кавказ эрдоган - это тюркский народ ты
what yes He is a Muslim he will liberate
что да Он мусульманин он освободит
The Great Padishah Erdogan will liberate the Caucasus
Великий падишах эрдоган освободит Кавказ
from the Russian ruler not a disgrace I
от Русского владетель не позор я тебя
beg you At least record this video don't
умоляю Ты хотя бы запишешь это видео не
disgrace yourself At least watch watch I will
позорься Хотя бы посмотри посмотри я
say So you are a disgrace Abbas of the people you are a
скажу Так ты позор аббасс народа ты
disgrace now let everyone watch in Turkey
позор сейчас пусть смотрят все в Турции
all Circassians all Abaza  all apsu are watching
все черкесы все абазы все апсуа смотрят
what kind of star you have become I just don't know how
какой ста ты стал просто я не знаю как
just some kind of
просто какой-то
mountain You are not a person already understand you are not an
горный Ты не человек уже понимаешь ты не
abaz you betrayed you know what
абаз ты предал знаешь какая самая
was the most important thing for the abaz Especially you under the
главная была у абаз Особенно ты под
flag of those who they are abaz never
флагом тех кто они абазы никогда не
kissed Russian Never you are an
целовали русским Никогда ты не
aba
аба
better to kiss Russians than you You're in
луше русским целовать чем тебе Ты в
a T-shirt
футболке
Come on come on Kiss kiss
Давай давай Целуй
look Kiss Come on
целуй смотри Целуй Давай у
you've never
тебя ни разу не
grown you're not an
выросло ты не
Ozi dog Look you've let yourself down you
Ози собачи Смотри ты ты себя опустил ты
said that you'll kiss Russians You
сказал что ты будешь русским целовать Ты
said in your own words that you'll
сказал своими словами что ты будешь
kiss Russians all this is a disgrace to you
целовать русским всё это ты позор
Abaza people  shame
абазинского народа позор
you are not worthy of us Go under the
ты нас недостоин Иди под
flag look we have an Abazin
флагом смотрите у нас есть абазин
who admitted that he will kiss
который признался что он будет целовать
Russians you are a disgrace and Basco people are
русским ты позор а Баско народа
right on the peacekeeper
справ на миротворце
yes yes that's how
да да вот так
they climb there are 30,000 people left there
лезут они их осталось там 30.000 народа
and here he climbs that in
и вот он лезет что в
Ukraine the Russian Empire killed his
Украине Российская империя убивала его
ancestors  robbed robs and
предков грабила грабит и
now brings them to poverty and then
сейчас так доводит их к нищете а потом
for money They are going to kill People in Ukraine
за бабки Идут они убиват Люде в Украине
subscribe so that more Circassians of the ASO bases
подпишитесь чтоб больше черкесов баз АСО
can see this and what is Rashka doing to you
видели это да что с вами делает Рашка
Slava Ukraine write to my Telegram right
Слава Укра пись на мий Telegram прямо
now axis VN and
зараз ось ВН а
pok this is very and very important  YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through the scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people at times do not
багато вдео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams so for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you we Mali operational links are written
тоб мы Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right now and Popik there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми окм
video more  also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we will oblige you with constant
и мы повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational links
оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава украини подпишись
with
с